As I say in my latest book, what would the ancestors say?
We've been excellent.
We found a way to survive being stripped of our families, our language, and our gods.
We found a way to master the growth of crops that we couldn't consume.
We've been excellent.
We found a way to birth an entire new culture and ethnicity amidst the threat of death.
And you know what?
We're going to be celebrating that culture in Columbus, Ohio.
I'm coming through.
Yours truly, Amanda Seals, is coming through to the Ohio Black Expo Riverfront Culture Fest.
Say that fast 10 times.
It's going to be blacktastic.
It's going to be blacktacular.
It's going to be black expolent.
So go ahead and get your tickets at ohioblacexpo.com to join me on May 24th in Columbus.
Listen, you know we're out on that.
It's going to be a good old black time.